http://www.barbecuen.com/privacy.htm

The cooler weather is here and the weather is spectacular for outdoor cooking! Now, is the time to maximize your grill and savor the flavor.
Your Barbecue Super Store
So,
you may be thinking about becoming a barbecue judge ... or perhaps you just want
to know what it is that the judges are looking for (and tasting) when judging
great barbecue. Who are the table captains? And what do they do? Who officiates
the contests? Overcooked? Under cooked? Too Salty? Too flat tasting? Mushy?
Tough? and many more.
Check out the 2013 Judging Classes and find one near you!
Featured BBQ'n
Video
Learn to prepare the best barbecue chicken in the world!
Our Privace Statement
IT'S REAL SIMPLE.....
Nottingham Internet Resources, Barbecue'n On The Internet and The Barbecue Store are all committed to maintaining your confidence and trust.
Confidentiality Policy
It is our policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and email address and telephone number, are all private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location and is used only for the purposes for which you provide.
By way of example: a request to receive our
Smoke 'n Fire Enquirer, a request to receive a catalog, to reply to your request or to handle your concern.
If at any time you change your mind and be removed from the Smoke 'n Fire Enquirer, or correct your personal information, please do so online
No Release of Information to Third Parties
Personal information will not be released to third parties unless it is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.
No Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information
We do not use "cookies" or other tracking information on our site.
We do not track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. We do not collect email addresses.
Here's a great money saving idea.  Wood chips and chunks never go bad. So why not order them in money saving bulk boxes?  Simply keep them in a dry area and use as needed!
Click & Order Your Bulk Chips & Chunks TODAY
Bad Weather?  Too hot or cold? Know what your bbq pit is doing with these Wireless Thermometers
There's not a better BBQ glove. Stylish Suade, lined and double protected from the elements.
FlameX Leather Gloves
Get all of Smoky Hale's wisdom and become the best cook around. Learn to do it right!
When cold, romance or just having to burn something, our designer firepits will do it all.  Get free shipping on SoJoe FirePits today
Visit The Barbecue Store Today!
FREE WINE @ The Barbecue Store
CLICK HERE TO FIND OUT MORE
Subscribe now to The Smoke 'N Fire Enquirer, the Internet's most popular backyard grilling and barbecuing on-line tutorial and we'll send you FREE recipes, techniques and tips for preparing the finest outdoor meals. FREE!  See a
Sample
Newsletter
Names are really important because we give FREE STUFF away in our newsletters!
